[
  {
    "category": "Know Your History",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What year was the first AWS re:Invent held?",
        "answer": 2012,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Who is the greater man ?",
        "answer": "Walter!",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": []
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What world record was set at the 2017 re:Invent Tatonka Challenge?",
        "answer": "Largest chicken wing eating contest: 214 people",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "wing eating contest",
          "largest wing eating contest",
          "biggest wing eating contest",
          "largest chicken wing eating contest",
          "biggest chicken wing eating contest",
          "wing eating competition",
          "largest wing eating competition",
          "biggest wing eating competition",
          "largest chicken wing eating competition",
          "biggest chicken wing eating competition"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Which year were both the ECS (Elastic Container Service) and Lambda announced at re:Invent?",
        "answer": 2014,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "The Main Event",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 5,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What webinar helps people learn about re:Invent leading up to the big event?",
        "answer": "How to re:Invent",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": ["how to reinvent"]
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "How many casinos does the re:Invent campus span this year (2018)?",
        "answer": 7,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What year did twitch.tv/aws start streaming at re:Invent?",
        "answer": 2016,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "How many chalk talks are scheduled for re:Invent 2018?",
        "answer": 592,
        "answerType": "NUMBER"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Let's Get Musical",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 9,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What genre of music is historically chosen for the re:play party?",
        "answer": "EDM",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "electronica",
          "DJ",
          "electronic dance music",
          "electronic music",
          "house music",
          "house"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Who usually announces the DJ for re:play?",
        "answer": "Werner Vogels",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": ["Werner"]
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What venue hosts the re:play party?",
        "answer": "The Linq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": ["the link", "linq", "link"]
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "Who was the re:play DJ at the 2013 re:Invent?",
        "answer": "DeadMau5",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "deadmau5",
          "Joel Thomas Zimmerman",
          "Joel Zimmerman",
          "dead mouse",
          "deadmouse",
          "deadmous"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "People, Places, and Things",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 13,
        "points": 100,
        "question": "What sports star made a surprise experience at Midnight Madness in 2017?",
        "answer": "Shaq",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": ["Shaquille O'Neal", "DJ Shaquille O'Neal", "DJ Diesel", "Diesel", "DJ Shaq"]
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "points": 200,
        "question": "Which AWS Engineer both appeared in the 2018 keynote, and also wrote this demo?",
        "answer": "Clare Liguori (hi!)",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": [
          "Clare Liguori",
          "Clare",
          "clareliguori",
          "clare_liguori",
          "Claire Liguori",
          "Claire",
          "claireliguori",
          "claire_liguori"
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "points": 300,
        "question": "What restaurant is located in both the Venetian and the Palazzo?",
        "answer": "Grand Lux Cafe",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": []
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "points": 400,
        "question": "What AWS speaker keynoted \"Tuesday Night Live\" in 2016?",
        "answer": "James Hamilton",
        "answerType": "STRING",
        "alternativeAnswers": []
      }
    ]
  }
]
